luluandgeorgia.com 2013-04-24

# Privacy Policy | Lulu and Georgia

**Privacy Policy**

**We value your privacy**

Lulu & Georgia is committed to keeping your personal and confidential information just that – personal and confidential. Your personal information is only required when you place an order, fill out a wishlist, or create a customer account. We use the information you provide to process and ship orders, and to contact you if necessary. You can sign up for our mailing list without having to worry that we're selling your personal information to any third parties; rest assured, we're not. 

**Security Policy**

We have taken every precaution to ensure that online shopping at Lulu & Georgia is as secure as possible. We use Secure Socket Layering (SSL), the industry standard encryption technology that ensures safe internet transmission of your personal information. When you place items in our shopping cart and purchase those items, your connection to our server becomes secure. To confirm this, look at the bottom part of your browser window. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), you can be sure that your information is secure. You can also ensure security by checking the URL line of your browser. When you enter the secure area of our site, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https." If for some reason you do not see these cues please contact us directly to place your order.

**About Cookies and JavaScript**

"Cookies" are small amounts of data that are stored on your computer in your internet browser. Cookies give us information about your activity on our Web site, which helps us improve the site and make it easier to use. We never use cookies to save passwords, credit card numbers, or other highly confidential information. Our web site also requires that JavaScript is enabled on your browser. Our servers use JavaScript to provide a more interactive shopping experience. Enabling this coding language on your browser will not affect performance, nor will it collect or store any of your personal information.

**Personal information collected**

Whenever you shop with Lulu & Georgia, we obtain from you the information we need to complete your transaction. This may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card number. We also keep records of your specific product purchases and transactions with us. We use this information to process your purchase transactions, to send you marketing and promotional materials by email, and to help us improve our online product assortments and services. You always have the option to opt out of mailings, and we never share or sell any of our customers' information.

**Opt out procedures**

We send promotional emails to you only if you have asked to receive them. Each time you receive an email from us, you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out," or stop receiving them. Simply follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email or contact us to remove your name from our mailing list.

**Links to other sites**

We like to share information about other hip and stylish websites that we think our customers may be interested in. Lulu & Georgia is not responsible for these sites. Please make sure that you carefully check out these sites and their individual privacy policies. 

**Policy changes**

We may choose to amend our Privacy Policy for various reasons. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post the change on our website. Once a new policy is posted it becomes effective immediately.  

Please feel fee to contact us via email to share your thoughts, comments and suggestions. We would love to hear from you!

Lulu & Georgia

8900 Melrose Ave

West Hollywood, CA 90069

Email: [contact@luluandgeorgia.com](mailto:contact@luluandgeorgia.com)

**Supplier inquiries**

For further information on any of our suppliers, artisans, or craftsmen, including applicable warranty information, please email us at [contact@luluandgeorgia.com](mailto:contact@luluandgeorgia.com).

**Press inquiries**

Please contact us via email at [rugsilove@luluandgeorgia.com](mailto:rugsilove@luluandgeorgia.com) with any press inquiries and we will be pleased to assist.

**Report technical issues**

For any problems with our website, please contact our webmaster at [support@luluandgeorgia.com](mailto:support@luluandgeorgia.com).
